Robert Winslow Gordon papers
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 8: Card Catalog, undated
  - Song index, Ni - Pe, Approximately 1,022 cards (Box 44)
  - Song index, Pf - So, Approximately 1,058 cards (Box 45)
  - Song index, Sp - Wam, Approximately 912 cards (Box 46)
  - Song index, Wan - Z, Approximately 949 cards (Box 47)